https://bruce-mclaren.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy – Bruce McLaren
compare
Email info@bruce-mclaren.com Call Us+64 (09) 280 6586HomeAbout1959 Sebring GP Win1962 Monaco GP Win1966 Le Mans Win1968 McLaren maiden win at Spa-FrancorchampsAutobiographyBiographyBruce McLaren Heritage CentreHistorical BooksPersonal TapesThe Cooper DaysThe DocumentaryRacing TeamCan-AmCan-AmClockwork OrangeMcLaren Can AmMcLaren M20McLaren OffensiveThe latest and greatest Can-Am carThe Worlds Fastest Sports CarVictory to HulmeFormula 1McLaren Formula 1McLaren M7A, B, C & M9AIndy 500People & PersonalitiesTeam Car HistoryThe CarsCan Am CarsCooperCooperThe 1960 2.5 Litre Cooper-ClimaxFormula 1 CarsFormula 2McLaren Formula 2Formula A/5000/LibreIndy 500 CarsList by NameMcLaren Olds Sports CarsOwners RegisterRoad CarsScale ModelsSports CarsTrojanThe TrustAims & ObjectivesBecome a MemberCorporate SponsorsOverviewPatrons and CommitteesNewsLatest NewsNewslettersEventsUpcoming EventsGalleryLinksPrivacy PolicyShopShopDonationsBasketMy accountShipping & HandlingContactMEMBERSJOIN USMy ProfileMy BILLING INFORMATIONMy INVOICELogInPrivacy PolicyHome / Privacy PolicyPrivacy Policy StatementPRIVACYYour privacy is taken very seriously any and all information collected online, including newsletter subscriptions or email addresses will be kept confidential by Bruce McLaren Trust and will not be sold, rented, loaned, or otherwise disclosed.When you visit our website, we record your visit and log the following information for statistical purposes – the user’s server address, the user’s top level domain name (for example .com, .gov, .nz, .uk etc), the data and time of visit to the site, and the type of browser used.Bruce McLaren Trust only records your email address if you send us a message. It is only used for correspondence with you and providing you with information associated with Bruce McLaren Trust and it’s direct associates.We will not use your email address or any of your personal details your email contains for any other purpose without your consent and we will not disclose your email address without your consent.COOKIESA cookie is a a brief bit of data that is sent between a web server and a web browser on the user’s machine, when the user visits a website. The cookie may be stored on the user’s machine while shopping is in progress to keep a reminder of the goods in the shopping trolley or to recognise the user on their return to the shop.  It is NOT an executable program and cannot do anything to your machine. Note, the website (server) cannot find out a name or email address, or anything about a user’s computer, by using cookies. All information obtained is information that you supply by completing forms, e.g. during registration.Login|Logout|Register|Profile
Search for:
Copyright © 2019 | Design Solutionz | All Rights Reserved HomeAbout1959 Sebring GP Win1962 Monaco GP Win1966 Le Mans Win1968 McLaren maiden win at Spa-FrancorchampsAutobiographyBiographyBruce McLaren Heritage CentreHistorical BooksPersonal TapesThe Cooper DaysThe DocumentaryRacing TeamCan-AmCan-AmClockwork OrangeMcLaren Can AmMcLaren M20McLaren OffensiveThe latest and greatest Can-Am carThe Worlds Fastest Sports CarVictory to HulmeFormula 1McLaren Formula 1McLaren M7A, B, C & M9AIndy 500People & PersonalitiesTeam Car HistoryThe CarsCan Am CarsCooperCooperThe 1960 2.5 Litre Cooper-ClimaxFormula 1 CarsFormula 2McLaren Formula 2Formula A/5000/LibreIndy 500 CarsList by NameMcLaren Olds Sports CarsOwners RegisterRoad CarsScale ModelsSports CarsTrojanThe TrustAims & ObjectivesBecome a MemberCorporate SponsorsOverviewPatrons and CommitteesNewsLatest NewsNewslettersEventsUpcoming EventsGalleryLinksPrivacy PolicyShopShopDonationsBasketMy accountShipping & HandlingContactMEMBERSJOIN USMy ProfileMy BILLING INFORMATIONMy INVOICELogIn
0
